Register to the Papers of Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
Yale University Music Library
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1890-1991; Series I; 32 boxes (13.3')
  - CORRESPONDENCE - By subject, I.B
    - Horowitz Golden Jubilee Concert 1928-1978 - ticket complaints and fan, 71 items. (Box 28, Folder 357)
      Includes 8 enclosures and 13 Vladimir Horowitz replies (drafts, some in Vladimir Horowitz's hand)
    - September 24, 1978 televised concert from Avery Fisher Hall - Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No. 3 - personal, 21 items. (Box 28, Folder 358)
    - September 24, 1978 televised concert from Avery Fisher Hall - Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto No. 3 - fan, 1978-1979; 38 items. (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - January 1979 recovery from operation, 1978-1979; 24 items. (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - CAMI (Columbia Artists Management Inc.), 1981-1988; 108 items. (Box 28, Folder 361)
      Includes 33 Vladimir Horowitz replies, 21 enclosures, 3 sheets of notes, and 5 printed acknowledgment cards from Vladimir Horowitz
    - May 1982 - London, 2 items. (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - June 1983 - Tokyo, 10 items. (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Legal - Moss - Chopin 90 minute cassette, 1984; 4 items. (Box 28, Folder 364)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1984- personal, 25 items. (Box 28, Folder 365)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday - October 1, 1984 - fan, 13 items. (Box 28, Folder 366)
    - Requests for photographs, etc., 1984-1985; 16 items. (Box 28, Folder 367)
    - April 1986 Moscow concert, 45 items. (Box 28, Folder 368)
    - Horowitz in Moscow, 1986; 48 items. (Box 28, Folder 369)
      18 enclosures
    - May 1986 Berlin concert - personal, 1986 May; 9 items. (Box 28, Folder 370)
    - May 1986 Berlin concert - fan, 1986 May; 46 items. (Box 28, Folder 371)
    - May 11, 1986 Hamburg concert - personal, 16 items. (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - May 11, 1986 Hamburg concert - fan, 37 items. (Box 29, Folder 373)
      6 enclosures
    - June 1, 1986 London concert, 7 items. (Box 29, Folder 374)
    - June 1986 Tokyo concert, 9 items. (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1986 - personal, 34 items. (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1986 - fan, 3 items. (Box 29, Folder 377)
    - October 5, 1986 White House recital, 4 items. (Box 29, Folder 378)
    - November 1986 Amsterdam concert - personal, 1986 Nov.; 16 items. (Box 29, Folder 379)
    - November 1986 Amsterdam concert - fan, 17 items. (Box 29, Folder 380)
    - November 1986 Frankfurt concert - personal, 1986 Nov.; 6 items. (Box 29, Folder 381)
    - November 1986 Frankfurt concert - fan, 1986 Nov.; 15 items. (Box 29, Folder 382)
    - 1986 tour - general correspondence, 6 items. (Box 29, Folder 383)
    - Christmas 1986, 1986 Dec.; 56 items. (Box 29, Folder 384)
    - June 1987 Hamburg concert - personal, 5 items. (Box 29, Folder 385)
    - June 1987 Hamburg concert - fan, 28 items. (Box 29, Folder 386)
    - May 24, 1987 Amsterdam concert - personal, 10 items. (Box 29, Folder 387)
    - May 24, 1987 Amsterdam concert - fan, 14 items. (Box 29, Folder 388)
    - May 31, 1987 Vienna concert - personal, 1987 May; 14 items. (Box 29, Folder 389)
    - May 31, 1987 Vienna concert - fan, 33 items. (Box 29, Folder 390)
    - June 1987 Berlin - "after Mrs. H. left", 34 items. (Box 29, Folder 391)
    - May/June 1987 tour correspondence, 33 items. (Box 29, Folder 392)
    - March 1987 Milan recording/filming of Mozart piano concerto K. 488, 1987-1988; 21 items. (Box 29, Folder 393)
      19 enclosures
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1987 - personal, 38 items. (Box 29, Folder 394)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1987 - fan, 8 items. (Box 29, Folder 395)
    - Deutsche Grammophon - general, 1987-1988; 25 items. (Box 29, Folder 396)
      Includes 20 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 2 enclosures
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1988, 99 items. (Box 29, Folder 397)
    - November 10, 1988 - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 398)
    - 55th wedding anniversary, December 21, 1988, 36 items. (Box 30, Folder 399)
      9 enclosures
    - Christmas 1988 - personal, 1988 Dec.; 65 items. (Box 30, Folder 400)
    - Christmas 1988 - fan, 1988-1989; 4 items. (Box 30, Folder 401)
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1989 - personal, 60 items. (Box 30, Folder 402)
      Includes 7 Vladimir Horowitz replies
    - Vladimir Horowitz birthday October 1, 1989 - fan, 8 items. (Box 30, Folder 403)
    - Condolences for Vladimir Horowitz's death - personal, 1989-1990; 490 items. (Box 30, Folder 404-416)
    - Condolences for Vladimir Horowitz's death - fan, 1989-1990; 57 items. (Box 31, Folder 417-423)
      11 enclosures
    - National Medal of Arts, 1990; 2 items. (Box 31, Folder 424)
- PROGRAMS AND PROGRAM NOTES, 1914-1991; Series II; 11 boxes (4.6')
  This series is divided into three subseries: A. Programs; B. Lists of Programs; and C. Analytical Notes. The bulk of the programs are for performances by Horowitz, with some programs by others at the end. Subseries A is listed chronologically. Subseries B includes various lists of Horowitz's performances arranged alphabetically by city or chronologically. Subseries C includes analytical program and liner notes arranged chronologically.
  A pencil note has been made on programs which were originally in the scrapbooks.
  - Programs, II.A
    - 1914-1926, 36 items. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1926, 8 items. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 1927, 9 items. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 1928-1929, 6 items. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 1930, 5 items. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 1931, 9 items. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 1932, 10 items. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 1933, 10 items. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1934, 11 items. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1935, 24 items. (Box 32, Folder 10-11)
    - 1936, 13 items. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - 1938, 14 items. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - 1939, 17 items. (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 1940, 22 items. (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
    - 1941, 25 items. (Box 33, Folder 17-18)
    - 1942, 20 items. (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - 1943, 29 items. (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - 1944, 21 items. (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - 1945, 19 items. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - 1946, 20 items. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - 1947, 31 items. (Box 34, Folder 24-25)
    - 1948, 39 items. (Box 34, Folder 26-27)
    - 1949, 48 items. (Box 35, Folder 28-30)
    - 1950, 42 items. (Box 35, Folder 31-33)
    - 1951, 30 items. (Box 36, Folder 34-35)
    - 1952, 22 items. (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - 1953, 13 items. (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - 1965, 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - 1966, 6 items. (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - 1967, 5 items. (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - 1968, 11 items. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - 1969, 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - 1974, 4 items. (Box 36, Folder 43)
      1974 Nov. 17 inscribed by Vladimir Horowitz to Sonia Horowitz
    - 1975, 11 items. (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - 1976, 17 items. (Box 37, Folder 45-46)
    - 1977, 10 items. (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - 1978, 19 items. (Box 37, Folder 48-49)
    - 1979, 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - 1980, 9 items. (Box 38, Folder 51)
    - 1981, 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 52)
    - 1982, 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 53-54)
    - 1983, 7 items. (Box 38, Folder 55-56)
    - 1985, 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 57)
    - 1986, 12 items. (Box 39, Folder 58-60)
    - 1987, 4 items. (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - n.d., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Others, 1921-1991; 9 items. (Box 39, Folder 63)
      See also: IX. MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS - Items pertaining to Arturo Toscanini - Falstaff program
  - Lists of Programs, II.B
    - Chronological lists, 1949-1953; 8 items; 28 cm. (Box 40, Folder 64-65)
      Typescript with pencil notes
    - Programs including some analytical notes arranged chronologically, 1966-1985; 91 items; 28-32 cm. (Box 40, Folder 66-74)
      Typescript and manuscript (in part, photocopies), and clippings from printed programs
    - Alphabetical list of 155 cities/halls with chronological list of concerts for each city, 1929-1953; 1 item; 258 cards; 20 cm. (Box 41, Folder 75-78)
      Typescript
    - Programs arranged alphabetically by city, 1965-1975; 28 items; 28 cm. (Box 41, Folder 79)
      Manuscript (photocopies)
    - Contents of notebook containing alphabetical list of cities/concert/halls with chronological list of concerts for each city, 1928-1980; 1 item; 22-28 cm. (Box 41, Folder 80)
    - Lists of recital programs by Vladimir Horowitz, 1934, n.d.; 12 items; 8 p.; 18-28 cm. (Box 41, Folder 81)
      Holographs in pencil and ink
  - Analytical Notes, II.C
    - Analytical notes by Olin Downes arranged chronologically, 1942-1953; 23 items. (Box 42, Folder 82-83)
    - Analytical notes by Olin Downes arranged alphabetically by composer, 54 items; 55 cards; 20 cm. (Box 42, Folder 84-87)
      Typescript and printed program, clipped, and pasted on card
    - Printed analytical notes by Olin Downes, some clipped, 23 items. (Box 42, Folder 88)
    - Miscellaneous liner notes, 1966-1969; 9 items; 28 cm. (Box 42, Folder 89)
      Typescript (in part, photocopies)
      Includes note to Vladimir Horowitz and cover letter
    - Horowitz in Concert 1967-1968, ca. 1968; 1 item; 5 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 42, Folder 90)
      First Recordings by Thomas Frost Typescript (copy)
    - Liner notes by Thomas Frost for The Studio Recordings 1985, 1986., 1 item; 6 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 42, Folder 91)
    - Analytical liner notes for The Last Recording by Murray Perahia, 1990 Jan.; 1 item; 4 sheets; 31 cm. (Box 42, Folder 91)
      Holograph (photocopy) Fax to Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
    - (Notes for Horowitz recording) by Vladimir Horowitz, n.d.; 1 item; 6 sheets; 28 cm. (Box 42, Folder 92)
      Typescript (copy) Mozart/Schubert
    - Analytical liner notes for Horowitz Encores (from his 1966 Carnegie Hall Recitals April 17, November 27 and December 10), 1 item; [7] sheets; 28 cm. (Box 42, Folder 92)
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1885-1991; Series III; 20 boxes (8.3')
  The photographs are divided into five subseries: A. Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, and Others; B. Others; C. Concert Halls, Ticket Lines, Places, and Objects; D. Toscanini Photographs; and E. Photo Albums. Subseries A is arranged chronologically, subseries B is arranged alphabetically, and subseries C, D, and E, are arranged chronologically.
  Negatives are noted and included in the item count. Prints were made and added to the Papers for the slides and negatives which were originally without prints.
  Dates, names, and other information is supplied, when possible, in brackets on the back of each photograph and or on the acid-free envelope or wrapper.
  The photographs in the albums in subseries E have been removed for preservation purposes, photographed, and the negatives are laid in.
  Oversize photographs are housed in an oversize box (133) at the end with other oversize boxes. The exceptions to this are the oversize photographs which are too large for a box. One photograph is housed in an oversize folder (ovf), and one framed photograph is stored separately in the Music Library.
  - Photographs: Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, and Others, III.A
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and others, 1912 and earlier; 20 items. (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Milan - 10 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1915; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Kiev - negative laid in
    - Russian document, 1915; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1921 or 1922; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1922 Mar. 22; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Photograph of photograph with note from Vladimir Horowitz to A. Petrovskii, Tiflis
    - Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1922-1923?; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, A. Glazunov, N. Milstein, and ?, 1923 Dec. 16; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Two photographs, one a copy of a photograph in the USSR archive and photocopy, the other from the same time but with an unidentified young man, Petrograd
    - Photocopy of silhouette of Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1923; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1924; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, before 1925; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Russia - negative laid in
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1926?; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Levanto - negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1926; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Berlin
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1926 or 1927; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Berlin - 3 copies and 2 negatives
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Alexander Merovich, and others, 1927 Mar. 23; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Tivoli/ Villa d'Este
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Nathan Milstein, and Alexander Merovich, and others, 1927; 14 items. (Box 43, Folder 4)
      Juan Les Pins
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1927; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Portrait by Aboaf, New York - glass negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Mme. Rostand-Mante, and others, 1927 or 1928; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1927 or 1928; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Germany
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1928; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Glass negative laid in
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1928; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and ?, 1929; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Arrowhead Lake
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1929; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Torn
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and others, 1929-1930; 24 items. (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Vesuvio, Capri - 12 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and others, 1920s; 21 items. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      Includes 9 negatives
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Ignaz Friedman, A. Glazunov, A. Merovich, and ?, pre 1930; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1930; 1 item. (Box 133, Folder 1)
      Paris
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1930-1932?; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Hrand, photographer, Paris
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1930; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Antibes
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Gregor Piatigorsky, Nathan Milstein, 1930; 2 items. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      New York - negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1930 or 1931; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1931 Oct. 18; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Musikhalle, Hamburg.
      Taken by Dr. Gerhard Buchholz.
      1986 concert in Hamburg
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1931; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 9)
      Lugano
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1932; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, 1933 Nov.; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 10)
      News Photos, London - copy and negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and ?, 1933 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
      Scotland
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1933; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Arturo Toscanini, Walter Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, Nathan Milstein, Mrs. Milstein, Gregor Piatigorsky, Mr. and Mrs. Molinari?, Anna Polo, and others, 1933; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1933; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, ca. 1933; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1933?; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1934 Jan.; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Honeymoon
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1934; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz and Sonia Horowitz, 1934; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1934; 4 items. (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Butin, photographer
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, and Simeon Horowitz, 1935 Jan.; 3 items. (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Queen's Hall, London Two copies laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, and Gregor Piatigorsky, 1935; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Italy
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Sonia Horowitz, 1935 June; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Venice - 2 negatives and 4 prints.
      See also: III.E.
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Sonia Horowitz, 1935 Aug.; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Cortina. See also: III.E.
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Gregor Piatigorsky, and Emanuela Castelbarco Acquarone, 1935 Aug.; 78 items. (Box 43, Folder 13-15)
      Cortina - 39 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Nathan Milstein, and others, 1935 Nov. 26; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 16)
      Inkey Tibor, photographer, Budapest - on bottom right corner of 1 photo: Városi Szinház Budapest 1935. Nov. 26.
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, ca. 1935 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 16)
      Photo for Vanity Fair
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1935; 4 items. (Box 44, Folder 16)
      Studio Seidenberg, Paris, possibly 1937-1938?, 4 copies
    - Sonia Horowitz, 1936-1937; 6 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
      Paris - 2 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Wally Toscanini Castelbarco, and Count and Emanuela Castelbarco, 1937 Mar.; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 17)
      Isolina S. Giovanni
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, 1937; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
      Salzburg
    - Vladimir Horowitz and [Enrico Polo], 1937; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1937; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1937; 3 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
      Petri, photographers, Milan
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1937; 12 items. (Box 44, Folder 17)
      Lucerne - 6 negatives laid in
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, 1937-1938; 12 items. (Box 44, Folder 18)
      Isolino S. Giovanni, Bagnoles? - 6 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1938; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 18)
      Gstaad
    - Sonia Horowitz, 1938; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 18)
      Gstaad - negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Arturo Toscanini, and others, 1939 Aug. 29; 10 items. (Box 44, Folder 19)
      Lucerne - negative laid in
    - Arturo Toscanini, Vladimir Horowitz, and Bruno Walter, 1939 Dec.; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 19)
      Rothschild Photo - Los Angeles
      2 photographs, negative, and print
    - Arturo Toscanini and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1939 Dec.; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 19)
      Otto Rothschild, photographer, Los Angeles
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1939; 17 items. (Box 44, Folder 20)
      Max Munn Autrey, photographer, Hollywood
      3 photographs and 13 copies
    - Sonia Horowitz, 1939; 4 items. (Box 44, Folder 20)
      Gstaad - 2 negatives laid in.
    - Sonia Horowitz, Emanuela Castelbarco Acquarone, 1939; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 20)
      Kastanienbaum? - negative laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1930s?; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Sonia Horowitz, 1930s; 6 items. (Box 44, Folder 21)
      Gstaad? - 3 negatives
    - Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, and Emanuela Castelbarco, 1930s; 12 items. (Box 44, Folder 21)
      6 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Eugene List, 1941; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 22)
      California?
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Toscanini, 1941; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1941?; 3 items. (Box 44, Folder 22)
      Hollywood Bowl?
      negative and print laid in.
      From V. SCRAPBOOKS. #2
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, and others, 1941; 48 items. (Box 44, Folder 23)
      California
      24 negatives laid in.
      See also: III.E. Photo Albums
    - Sonia Horowitz, Arturo Toscanini, Carla Toscanini, and others, 1942 Apr.; 20 items. (Box 44, Folder 24)
      Riverdale - Sonia Horowitz's first communion - 10 negatives laid in.
      See also: III.E. Photo albums
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1942; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 25)
      Philadelphia
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Rachmaninoff, and Walt Disney, 1942; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1943-1944; 6 items. (Box 44, Folder 25)
      Photograph of portrait by Eugene Spiro - 3 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Mrs. Rachmaninoff, and Arthur Rodzinski, 1943 or 1944; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 25)
      Copy laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1944; 5 items. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1944-1945?; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Manuel Rosenthal and 2 others, 1945 Summer; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 26)
      Bretton Woods
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1945; 18 items. (Box 44, Folder 26)
      Carlyle Studios, New York
      6 photographs with 10 copies of one laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz and window displays, ca. 1946 May 13; 6 items. (Box 44, Folder 27)
      RCA Victor photo and window displays at shops in New York and Philadelphia
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1946 Aug.; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 27)
      Port Kent, N.Y.
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Vladimir Golschmann and ?, 1946; 9 items. (Box 44, Folder 27)
      Port Kent, N.Y.?
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1946; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 27)
      New York
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1946; 4 items. (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1947 Jan. 17?; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 27)
      Hill Auditorium?
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1947?; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and others, 1947; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1947; 20 items. (Box 44, Folder 28)
      Alan Fontaine, photographer
      2 photographs with several copies of each - stamped "Annie Friedberg"
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1947; 9 items. (Box 133, Folder 3-4)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Sonia Horowitz, ca. 1948 July 1; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 29)
      George Valentine Enell and Assoc., Inc., New York, inscribed by Vladimir Horowitz to Sonia Horowitz
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Sonia Horowitz, 1948; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, and Sonia Horowitz, 1948; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 29)
      New York apartment in front of a Picasso, 5 copies
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Arthur Rodzinski, 1948; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 29)
      Robert Marsh, photographer - rehearsing Rachmaninoff Third
    - Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1948 Aug. 3; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1948 or 1949; 6 items. (Box 45, Folder 30)
      Franklin Studios - 4 copies and a negative laid in - stamped "Annie Friedberg"
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, and others, 1948 or 1949; 20 items. (Box 45, Folder 31)
      George Junior Republic? - 10 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, Sonia Horowitz, Nathan Milstein, and others, 1948 or 1949; 40 items. (Box 45, Folder 32-33)
      20 negatives laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1949 Apr.; 4 items. (Box 45, Folder 34)
      Chicago
    - Vladimir Horowitz and William Steinberg, 1949; 2 items. (Box 45, Folder 34)
      [Hollywood Bowl?]
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1940s; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Vladimir Horowitz and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1940s; 8 items. (Box 45, Folder 34)
      RCA Victor photograph
    - Vladimir Horowitz, Fritz Reiner, and the Pittsburgh Symphony, 1940s; 8 items. (Box 45, Folder 34)
      Pittsburgh
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1940s; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Franklin Studios -3 copies, negative laid in - stamped "Annie Friedberg"
    - Vladimir Horowitz, 1940s; 15 items. (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Karsh, photographer, Ottawa
      2 photographs, 4 copies of one, 4 of the other, and negative in poor condition laid in
    - Vladimir Horowitz, [1940s]; 1 item. (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Photo of portrait
    - Vladimir Horowitz and others, [1940s]; 5 items. (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Bernard Photographers, Houston